- Looks like she worked out a little too much.
看起来她锻炼得有点过头了。
Scary, huh?
吓人吧？
- Actually, you know what the scariest thing about Halloween is?
实际上，你知道万圣节最可怕的是什么吗？
- Pfft, last year's quadcopus costume.
噗，去年的四轴章鱼装。
All: Trick or treat?
大家：不给糖就捣蛋？
- Worst costume ever, Harpers.
最糟糕的服装，哈珀斯。
- Eight tentacles but only one bag.
八条触手却只有一个袋子。
What were we thinking?
我们当时在想什么？
- I was gonna say the scariest thing about Halloween is that.
我本来想说万圣节最可怕的就是那个。
- Bubbling brew, dark and oozy.
冒泡的药水，黑暗又黏稠。
Who would like a trick-or-treat smoothie?
谁想来一杯捣蛋或糖果的冰沙？
[cackling]
[咯咯笑]
Too much trick?
捣蛋成分太多了？
- [sighs] Tom,
- [叹气] 汤姆，
when we agreed to dress as a witch and wizard,
当我们同意装扮成女巫和巫师时，
I thought it was clear which one of us would be the witch.
我以为很清楚我们中谁会是女巫。
- Sorry, Anne, but if we have to have another cackle-off,
- 抱歉，安妮，但如果我们必须再来一次咯咯笑比赛，
bring it!
放马过来！
- [cackling] - [cackling]
- [咯咯笑] - [咯咯笑]
[both cackling]
[两人咯咯笑]
- Correction--that's the scariest thing about Halloween.
- 更正——那才是万圣节最可怕的事情。
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
♪ ♪
- [whistling melody]
- [吹口哨的旋律]
♪ ♪
[rhythmic clapping] - ♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
[有节奏的拍手] - ♪ 一，二，三，四！ ♪
- [whistling melody]
- [吹口哨的旋律]
♪ ♪
- ♪ Na, na, na, na, na-na ♪
- ♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐-呐 ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na-na ♪
♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐-呐 ♪
- ♪ One, two ♪ - ♪ Na, na, na ♪
♪ 一，二 ♪ ♪ 呐，呐，呐 ♪
- ♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
♪ 一，二，三，四！ ♪
- Four Halloween smoothies, all treat, no trick.
四杯万圣节奶昔，全是甜头，没有花招。
- Thanks, Josie. Nice lunch lady costume.
谢谢，乔茜。午餐阿姨的装扮很棒。
- Oh, I'm not just any lunch lady.
哦，我不仅仅是普通的午餐阿姨。
I'm sloppy Josie.
我是邋遢的乔茜。
- By the way, we're really psyched
顺便说一下，我们真的很兴奋
you're DJ-ing our Halloween dance.
你能在我们的万圣节舞会上担任DJ。
- Oh, me too.
哦，我也是。
I just hope the DJ booth can fit all this lunch in my trunk.
我只希望DJ台能装下我后备箱里的所有午餐。
Boop!
嘟！
- I just hope the dance lives up to the hype.
我只希望舞会能不负众望。
- You know who has two thumbs and does live up to the hype?
你知道谁有两个拇指并且确实不负众望吗？
This guy!
就是这家伙！
And all everyone's talking about is who he's taking to the dance.
而且大家都在谈论他会带谁去舞会。
- Nobody's talking about that.
没人谈论那个。
- We're talking about it right now.
我们现在就在谈论。
- You don't need to take a date to the dance.
你不需要带约会对象去舞会。
- Most people may not, but most people ain't Dicky.
大多数人可能不需要，但大多数人不是迪基。
I have a reputation to uphold.
我有名声要维护。
- You're not the only one with two thumbs
- 你不是唯一一个有两根拇指的人
who's asking someone to the dance.
在邀请别人参加舞会。
- Really? Who else is?
- 真的吗？还有谁？
- This guy.
- 这家伙。
- Hey, look at us. A couple of this-guys.
- 嘿，看看我们。一对这家伙。
- Well, I'm keeping my options open.
- 嗯，我在保持我的选择开放。
Why dance with one goose
为什么要和一只鹅跳舞
when you can dance with the whole gaggle?
当你可以和整个鹅群跳舞？
- You guys are making me gaggle.
- 你们让我感到鹅群。
- Uh, hey, Dawn, do you know that kid over there?
- 呃，嘿，Dawn，你认识那边那孩子吗？
He keeps looking at you.
他一直在看你。
- Oh, that's Mack.
- 哦，那是Mack。
He sits in front of me in math class.
他在数学课上坐在我前面。
Awesome doodler, really smart, nice neck.
画画很棒，非常聪明，脖子很好看。
- Oh, well, don't look now,
- 哦，现在别回头看，
but Mr. Nice Neck is coming this way.
但是那位脖子好看的先生正朝这边走来。
- Hey, Dawn. - Uh, hey, Mack.
- 嘿，Dawn。 - 呃，嘿，Mack。
- Did you see the dude in the witch's costume?
- 你看到那个穿女巫服装的家伙了吗？
- I know. Glad he's not my dad.
- 我知道。很高兴他不是我爸爸。
- [cackling]
- [咯咯笑]
Hi, I'm Dawn's dad.
嗨，我是Dawn的爸爸。
Nice neck! You must be Mack.
脖子不错！你一定是Mack。
[chuckles]
[轻笑]
Oh. Awkward!
哦。真尴尬！
[cackling]
[咯咯笑]
- So, if you thought that was awkward,
- 如果你觉得刚才那很尴尬，
here comes this.
那接下来这个更尴尬。
Uh, at the Halloween dance,
呃，在万圣节舞会上，
I was thinking maybe you could save me a dance?
我在想，也许你能给我留一支舞？
- A dance? With you?
- 一支舞？和你？
- I knew it was a stupid idea.
- 我知道这是个愚蠢的主意。
- No, no, no. It's a good idea.
- 不，不，不。这是个好主意。
- So, yes?
- 那么，是的？
Great, I can't wait.
太好了，我迫不及待了。
- And we have a new scariest thing about Halloween.
- 而且我们有了万圣节最恐怖的事情。
- ♪ ♪
- Hey.
- 嘿。
You know what the best kind of Halloween candy is?
你知道最好的万圣节糖果是什么吗？
Me as your arm candy
我作为你的臂上糖果
when we walk into that dance.
当我们走进那个舞会时。
Now, let's hear how you're gonna ask your girl.
现在，让我们听听你要怎么邀请你的女孩。
- [takes a deep breath] Hello--
（深吸一口气）你好——
- [imitates buzzer]
（模仿蜂鸣器声）
What is this, 2012?
这是2012年吗？
Who says hello?
谁会说‘你好’？
- Fine.
好吧。
Will you go to the dance with me?
你愿意和我一起去参加舞会吗？
- [as a robot] Will you go to the dance with me?
（模仿机器人）你愿意和我一起去参加舞会吗？
Now you're embarrassing both of us.
现在你让我们俩都尴尬了。
You don't ask. You tell.
你不是问，而是告诉。
- I was just thinking--
我只是想——
- There's the problem.
问题就在这儿。
You're thinking.
你在思考。
Don't think. Think!
不要思考。要行动！
- I'm confused.
我糊涂了。
- Just be in the moment.
活在当下。
Never hesitate, never waver.
绝不犹豫，绝不摇摆。
- I got it! I think.
我明白了！我想。
- This is hopeless.
这真是无望。
- Who is it? Who is it? Who is it? Who is it?
是谁？是谁？是谁？是谁？
Who is it? - Uh-huh, uh-huh. We'd love to.
是谁？ - 嗯哼，嗯哼。我们很乐意。
- Love to what? Is that your mother? I'm not going there for Thanksgiving.
- 乐意什么？那是你妈妈吗？我可不去你家过感恩节。
- Shh! - No, I--I'm telling you, Anne.
- 嘘！ - 不，我——我告诉你，安妮。
I am not sleeping in that guest room.
我绝不会睡在那间客房里。
- Uh, sure, yeah, that's fine. - No, no, it's not fine.
- 呃，当然，好的，那没问题。 - 不，不，有问题。
The bed is lumpy, and that creepy little door
那床很硬，还有那扇
we're not allowed to open freaks me out!
我们不被允许打开的诡异小门让我毛骨悚然！
- Okay, see you later. Bye.
- 好吧，再见。
- Ugh, I will not go through this again.
- 呃，我不会再经历这种事了。
You know what, we're doing separate holidays this year.
你知道吗，今年我们各自过各自的节日。
- That was the school.
- 那是学校打来的。
They want us to chaperone the Halloween dance.
他们想让我们陪同参加万圣节舞会。
- Oh, a dance! Awesome!
- 哦，舞会！太棒了！
I was totally kidding about the separate holiday thing.
我完全是在开玩笑说分开过假期的事。
- Come on. You guys can't go to the dance.
- 拜托。你们不能去舞会。
- Yeah!
- 是啊！
- You're gonna cramp my style.
- 你们会破坏我的风格的。
- Mine too.
- 我的也是。
- There will be no cramping of anyone's style.
- 不会有人破坏任何人的风格。
Trust me-- your father and I know plenty
相信我——你爸爸和我非常清楚在舞会上被破坏风格的感觉。
about having our style cramped at a dance.
关于在舞会上我们的风格被压抑的事情。
- It was our senior prom.
- 那是我们的毕业舞会。
- ♪ ♪
- What is this? A Madonna video?
- 这是什么？一个麦当娜的视频吗？
No touching!
不许碰！
- So trust me, we understand.
- 所以相信我，我们理解。
We are not gonna get in your way.
我们不会妨碍你们的。
- And they're gone.
- 他们走了。
- [sighs] What's wrong?
- [叹气] 怎么了？
- Nothing. Why?
- 没什么。怎么了？
- Because I know you, Dawn.
因为我了解你，Dawn。
And when something's bothering you, you make origami animals.
而且当你有心事时，你会折纸动物。
- That is not true.
那不是真的。
Okay, a little true.
好吧，有一点是真的。
- Dawn.
Dawn。
- All right, a lot true!
好吧，非常真实！
- So what is it?
那么是什么事呢？
- Just-- I just can't tell you here.
只是——我不能在这里告诉你。
Come on.
来吧。
Mack asked me if I would save him a dance.
Mack问我是否愿意为他留一支舞。
I like Mack, and I really wanna dance with him, but...
我喜欢Mack，我真的想和他跳舞，但是...
I can't dance.
我不会跳舞。
- How bad can you be?
你有多糟糕？
Show me.
给我看看。
- Okay.
好吧。
But after you see what you're about to see,
但当你看到即将看到的东西后，
promise we'll still be friends?
答应我们还是朋友好吗？
[exhales]
（叹气）
- Oh, my.
哦，天哪。
What is happening?
发生了什么？
How does your leg do that?
你的腿是怎么做到的？
Why does your leg do that?
你的腿为什么会那样？
Stop your leg from doing that!
让你的腿别那样了！
- See?
看吧？
That's why I can't go to the dance.
这就是我不能去跳舞的原因。
- You can't miss our first school dance.
你不能错过我们的第一次学校舞会。
You just have to find a way of going
你只需要找到一种去的方式
but not do whatever that was.
但不要做刚才那样的动作。
- So it's as bad as I thought, huh?
所以情况和我预想的一样糟糕，是吧？
- You look like a baby deer being born.
你看起来像刚出生的小鹿。
- Never hesitate, never waver.
从不犹豫，永不动摇。
Never hesitate, never waver.
- You ready to ask your girl?
准备好问你的女孩了吗？
- Ready. You ready to ask yours?
准备好了。你准备好问你的了吗？
- Born ready.
天生就准备好了。
Both: There she is! What?
她在那儿！什么？
- I'm going to ask Scarlett. - I'm going to ask Scarlett.
我要去问Scarlett。
- [laughing] Oh, Ricky, Ricky, Ricky.
She's way out of your league.
哦，Ricky，Ricky，Ricky。
Think about it.
她完全超出你的级别。想想吧。
- You told me not to think!
- 你告诉我不许想！
- Hello, Scarlett.
- 你好，Scarlett。
- Uh, will you go to the dance with me?
- 呃，你能和我一起去跳舞吗？
- Will you go to the dance with me?
- 你能和我一起去跳舞吗？
- I asked first. - I got here first.
- 我先问的。 - 我先到的。
- Wow. I don't know what to say.
- 哇。我不知道该说什么。
- Say, "Yes, Dicky." - Say, "Yes, Ricky."
- 说，“好的，Dicky。” - 说，“好的，Ricky。”
- I'm going to say yes.
- 我要说好的。
Both: Yes!
- 好的！
To who?
- 对谁？
- To one of you. I just don't know which one.
对你们中的一个。我只是不知道是哪一个。
You're both so nice.
你们俩都这么好。
You know what?
你知道吗？
Just meet me before the dance, and I'll tell you guys then.
就在舞会前见我，到时我会告诉你们。
- I can't believe she didn't say yes.
我简直不敢相信她没有说好。
- I can't believe she didn't say no!
我简直不敢相信她没有拒绝！
- ♪ ♪
♪ ♪
- Well, Anne, we never got that dance on our prom night,
安妮，我们在毕业舞会之夜没有跳成那支舞，
but tonight, it's gonna happen.
但今晚，它就要发生了。
- I can barely breathe, Tom.
我几乎喘不过气来，汤姆。
- I feel the excitement too.
我也感到很兴奋。
- No, this dress is too tight!
不行，这裙子太紧了！
Oh!
哦！
Do we really have to wear our old prom clothes?
我们真的必须穿以前的舞会服装吗？
- Suck it up, Anne! We're recreating the magic.
忍一忍，安妮！我们要重现那份魔力。
Where's your sense of romance? Kids, come on!
你的浪漫情怀呢？孩子们，快点！
[latin music]
拉丁音乐
- Tonight, I dance.
今晚，我要跳舞。
♪ ♪
- Wow, honey. You look great.
哇，亲爱的。你看起来真棒。
What costumes did your brothers decide on?
你们兄弟俩决定穿什么服装？
- Well, they're both trying to impress Scarlett,
嗯，他们都想给Scarlett留下深刻印象，
so they decided to dress as the coolest person they know.
所以他们决定打扮成他们认识的最酷的人。
Dicky dressed as...
Dicky打扮成...
Dicky.
Dicky。
- [beatboxing]
（节奏口技）
- And Ricky dressed as...
而Ricky打扮成...
Also Dicky.
也是Dicky。
- [beatboxing]
（节奏口技）
- Looking good, bro.
看起来不错，兄弟。
But why would she go out with a counterficky-Dicky
但她为什么要和一个假迪基出去，
when she could have all 4'6" of the real deal?
而不是选择真正的4英尺6英寸的迪基呢？
- Well, let's just see which Dicky she pickys.
- 好吧，让我们看看她会选择哪个迪基。
- All right, let's get this show on the road.
- 好的，让我们开始吧。
- Yeah, let's go, guys, come on. Go, go, go.
- 是的，走吧，伙计们，快点。快，快，快。
- Where's Dawn?
- 道恩在哪里？
- Coming!
- 来了！
- Dawn!
- 道恩！
- [grunts] Still working out the kinks.
- [咕哝]还在调整。
- Oh, hey, hey! Dawn?
- 哦，嘿，嘿！道恩？
Okay, look, you can barely walk in this costume.
好吧，你看，你穿着这身服装几乎走不了路。
You won't be able to dance in it.
你穿着它没法跳舞。
- I won't be able to dance?
- 我没法跳舞？
I never thought of that!
我从来没想过这一点！
Oh, well, let's go.
哦，好吧，我们走吧。
Whoa! - Dawn!
哇！- 道恩！
- Argh, guard the house, matey.
- 啊，守好房子，伙计。
[barks]
[吠叫]
- ♪ ♪
- There she is.
- 她在那儿。
- Good luck, Dicky.
祝你好运，迪基。
- You too...Dicky.
你也是...迪基。
- Hey, Scarlett.
嘿，斯嘉丽。
- Hey, Dickys.
嘿，迪基们。
- Have you made up your mind?
你决定好了吗？
- I have,
我决定了，
and I'd like to go to the dance with Dicky.
我想和迪基一起去跳舞。
Both: Yes!
太好了！
Wait. Which Dicky?
等等。哪个迪基？
- Uh, the real one.
呃，真的那个。
- I understand.
我明白了。
Thank you for your consideration.
谢谢你的考虑。
Congratulations.
恭喜。
- So would you like to walk me into the dance?
那么，你愿意带我进舞会吗？
♪
- Dawn, that costume is
Dawn，那套服装真是
purrrrfect.
完美极了。
- Thanks.
谢谢。
I'd do a celebratory dance, but I can't.
我本想跳个庆祝舞，但我不能。
How great is that?
那有多棒？
- This is so embarrassing.
这太尴尬了。
- Hate all you want. I love life.
随你怎么讨厌。我喜欢生活。
- No, Scarlett totally rejected me and chose Dicky.
不，Scarlett完全拒绝了我，选择了Dicky。
Do you think everyone's talking about it?
你觉得大家都在谈论这件事吗？
- Relax. Nobody's talking about it.
放松。没人谈论这事。
- Psst. It's me, Dicky.
嘘。是我，Dicky。
- Really?
真的吗？
I thought it was a crow
我以为是一只乌鸦
with a Dicky costume on its butt.
屁股上穿着Dicky的服装。
- No, it's me.
不，是我。
- Where's Scarlett?
- 斯嘉丽在哪儿？
- The worst thing just happened.
- 刚刚发生了最糟糕的事。
When she chose me, I totally choked.
她选了我，我完全慌了。
Do you think everyone's talking about it?
你觉得大家都在议论这件事吗？
- What is with you guys? Nobody's talking about you.
- 你们怎么了？没人谈论你们。
[laughter]
[笑声]
- Worst dance fail ever, Harpers.
- 有史以来最糟糕的舞蹈失误，哈珀斯。
- You know what?
- 你知道吗？
You don't like what people are saying?
你不喜欢别人说的话？
Let's go change the conversation.
那我们就去改变话题吧。
With our hips! [latin music]
用我们的臀部！[拉丁音乐]
Ole!
- Let's get out of here.
- 我们离开这里吧。
- All right, party people! Lost and found alert.
- 好的，派对人士们！失物招领警报。
Somebody left their retainer in the punch bowl.
有人在潘趣酒碗里留下了他们的牙套。
Now it's time for DJ Sloppy Josie
现在是DJ Sloppy Josie的时间
to serve up some slow jams.
来播放一些慢节奏的情歌。
[romantic music]
[浪漫音乐]
♪ ♪
- Mrs. Harper, I believe we have some unfinished business.
- Harper太太，我相信我们还有一些未完成的事务。
[grunts]
[咕哝声]
- What is this? [both gasp]
- 这是什么？[两人惊呼]
A Madonna video?
麦当娜的录像？
Chaperones do not dance.
监护人是不跳舞的。
- Wow, great costume.
- 哇，服装真棒。
- You look just like our mean old chaperone, Ms. Rothschild.
- 你看起来就像我们那位严厉的老监护人，罗斯柴尔德女士。
- That was my mother.
- 那是我妈妈。
I took over her chaperoning business.
我接管了她的监护业务。
- [exhales] Nice lady.
- [叹气] 好女人。
[chuckles] Such a--such a sweet smile.
[轻笑] 多么——多么甜美的微笑。
Ha, yeah, that's the one!
哈，对，就是她！
- Hey, Dawn.
嘿，Dawn。
- Oh, hi.
哦，嗨。
Look at you,
看看你，
Mack in cheese.
奶酪里的麦奇。
- Look at you,
看看你，
jack in box.
盒子里的杰克。
- So look at us.
所以看看我们。
- So, you ready for that dance?
那么，你准备好跳舞了吗？
- I... - Uh-huh?
我... - 嗯？
- Would... - Uh-huh?
- Love... - I like where this is going.
- To... - Great!
- But... - Oh, no.
- It's this costume.
I didn't realize it'd be so hard to dance in.
Grr, stupid me. What was I thinking?
Guess I'm more of a jerk in the box.
- Come on. I'm sure you can dance a little.
- I don't get it.
Why'd you run?
你为什么要跑？
- I don't know. I just panicked.
- 我不知道。我只是慌了。
[girls laughing]
[女孩们笑]
- Now everybody's making fun of me.
- 现在每个人都在取笑我。
- Look, you're embarrassed, and I'm disappointed.
- 看，你感到尴尬，我也很失望。
Let's not let it ruin our night.
我们不要让它毁了我们的夜晚。
I'm here for you, no matter what.
我在这里支持你，无论发生什么。
- Hey, Ricky. Wanna dance?
- 嘿，Ricky。想跳舞吗？
- You bet.
- 当然想。
- He didn't hesitate.
- 他没有犹豫。
He didn't waver.
他毫不犹豫。
[sighs]
- Trick or beats!
不给糖就捣蛋！
[techno music]
- So... Here we are, on the dance floor.
那么...我们来到了舞池。
- Are you actually gonna dance?
你真的要跳舞吗？
- Oh, I am dancing!
哦，我正在跳舞！
There's things going on inside here you don't even know about.
这里面发生的事情你甚至都不知道。
- Looks like it's time for the spotlight dance.
看来是时候来个聚光灯下的舞蹈了。
All: Dance! Dance! Dance! Dance! Dance! Dance! Dance!
大家：跳舞！跳舞！跳舞！跳舞！跳舞！跳舞！跳舞！
- You know, if you didn't wanna dance with me,
you could've just said so.
- Mack?
- Psst, Ricky.
- Mom, you're cramping my style.
- Well, Ms. Rothschild's cramping my style.
I need your help. Pass this note to dad.
- Fine. - Thank you.
- Hey, pass this note to my dad.
He's the chaperone over by the snack table.
- Pass this to the chaperone at the snack table.
把这交给零食桌那边的监护人。
- Hey, give this to the old dude over by the snack table.
嘿，把这个给零食桌那边的老家伙。
- Mack? Mack?
麦克？麦克？
What are you doing back here?
你在这里做什么？
- Hiding. From my shame.
躲藏。因为我的羞愧。
What are you doing back here?
你在这里做什么？
- [sighs] Hoping to get a block of cheese to forgive me.
希望得到一块奶酪来原谅我。
All: Nicky! Nicky! Nicky! Nicky! Nicky!
尼基！尼基！尼基！尼基！
- How did Nicky become the life of the party?
尼基怎么成了派对的生命？
- And how did Ricky become a better Dicky than Dicky?
里基怎么比迪基还更像迪基？
I'm supposed to be the cool Harper.
我应该是酷酷的哈珀。
Now I'm the least cool Harper.
现在我是最不酷的哈珀。
- Oh, please.
哦，拜托。
I'm the least cool Harper.
我是最不酷的哈珀。
Have you ever seen me dance?
你见过我跳舞吗？
- Have you ever run away from a girl because you were scared?
你有没有因为害怕而从一个女孩身边跑开？
- No, but I made a guy run away from me because I was scared.
没有，但我让一个男人因为我害怕而跑开了。
Sometimes I wish I was more like Nicky.
有时候我希望我能更像尼基。
He just is who he is and doesn't care what anyone else thinks.
他只是做他自己，不在乎别人怎么想。
- I wish I was more like Ricky.
我希望我能更像瑞奇。
I should think.
我想也是。
Maybe if I had, I wouldn't have been freaked out
也许如果我有过，我就不会在斯嘉丽说愿意时吓坏了。
when Scarlett said yes.
我总是说大话，但从来没有人同意跟我玩。
I talk a big game, but nobody's ever agreed to play before.
叹气
- [sighs]
终于。哦。
- Finally. Oh.
我听说你想跟我跳舞。
- I hear you wanted to dance with me.
我只有一个规矩。
I just have one rule.
不要坠入爱河。
Don't fall in love.
哦，奥斯卡，奥斯卡，奥斯卡，
- Oh, Oscar, Oscar, Oscar,
我无法承诺这一点。
I can't promise that.
我不能保证这一点。
- I'm having fun.
我在玩得开心。
- Yeah, whatever.
是啊，随便吧。
- I can't believe Dicky just ran away like that.
我简直不敢相信迪基就这样跑了。
He's totally not the guy I thought he was.
他完全不是我想象中的那种人。
You're way cooler.
你比他酷多了。
- Coolest Harper ever, Harper.
最酷的哈珀，哈珀。
All: Yeah!
所有人：耶！
- Actually,
实际上，
the real reason Dicky ran away was because he's cool.
迪基逃跑的真正原因是因为他很酷。
When you chose him, he felt bad for me,
当你选择他时，他为我感到难过，
so he ran away to get people laughing at him instead of me.
所以他跑开是为了让人们嘲笑他而不是我。
- Okay, so he's the coolest Harper ever.
- 好吧，所以他是有史以来最酷的Harper。
- No, Ricky. You don't have to cover for me.
- 不，Ricky。你不必为我掩饰。
They're right.
他们是对的。
Ricky dressed like me because he wanted to go
Ricky打扮成我是因为他想以他所知道的最酷的人去参加。
as the coolest guy he knew.
但他穿错了服装。
But he wore the wrong costume.
伙计，你应该直接以你自己的样子去。
Dude, you should've just gone as yourself.
- 谢谢。
- Thanks.
- ♪ Ah, freak out ♪
♪ 啊，惊慌失措 ♪
♪ Le freak c'est chic ♪
♪ 惊慌失措，这很时髦 ♪
♪ Freak out ♪
♪ 惊慌失措 ♪
- Dawn, you don't have to do this.
Dawn，你不必这么做。
- Yes, I do, Mae.
不，我必须做，Mae。
Look away if you have to,
如果你必须的话，就转过头去，
but I'm letting Mack and the whole world see what I got.
但我要让Mack和全世界看到我拥有的。
Hey.
嘿。
- Hey.
Where's your costume?
你的服装呢？
- Okay.
好的。
I only wore that costume, so I wouldn't have to dance.
我穿那件服装，只是为了不用跳舞。
Truth is,
事实上，
I'm a really bad dancer, but I should've just told you that.
我跳舞真的很糟糕，但我应该早点告诉你的。
So if you're not too mad at me, I'd still like that dance.
所以如果你不介意的话，我还是想和你跳这支舞。
- [mouthing words]
（无声地说）
- Sure.
当然。
- That's right, people.
没错，各位。
This is me dancing.
这就是我在跳舞。
Know what? I don't know what I was so scared about.
你知道吗？我不知道我之前在害怕什么。
I kind of like this.
我有点喜欢这个。
♪
- Wow. I feel so much better.
- 哇。我感觉好多了。
- I appreciate it, but you don't have to dance badly for me.
- 我很感激，但你不必为我跳得这么糟糕。
- What?
- 什么？
- Nothing. - Okay.
- 没事。- 好的。
- ♪ Ah, freak out ♪
- ♪ 啊，尽情狂欢 ♪
- A little old man told me you wanted to see me.
- 有个小老头告诉我你想见我。
- I do.
- 是的，我要去钓鱼，汤姆。
I'm going fishing, Tom.
- Rothschild seems to have misplaced her yardstick.
罗斯柴尔德似乎弄丢了她的尺子。
[yardstick clatters]
[尺子掉落声]
We have some time. - [chuckles]
我们还有点时间。- [笑声]
[dress ripping] - Oh.
[裙子撕裂声] - 哦。
- Sorry.
- 对不起。
- No.
- 没关系。
I can finally breathe! -[both laugh]
我终于能呼吸了！-[两人笑]
- Here, here. Let's go. - Okay. Oh.
- 来，来。我们走吧。- 好的。哦。
- ♪ ♪
- [whistling melody]
- [吹口哨旋律]
♪ ♪
- [vocalizing]
- [发声]
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ 是的 ♪
[vocalizing]
[发声]
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ 是的 ♪
- ♪